

ABOUT:

I'm a young professional who is well skilled and detail oriented in the tech field. Being involved with computers and electronics for over 20 years, having learned skills from replacing/repairing hardware (desktop computers, laptops, smartphones) to installing operating systems (WIN/MAC), and writing code (JavaScript, Python, & HTML/CSS). Problem solving abilities come with ease. An opportunist to provide skills towards a well suited role.

CONTACT:

PHONE: 317-789-5478

E-MAIL: insighteuphoric@gmail.com

WEBSITE:

https://u4ik.github.io/

Hobbies

Audio Production Video Production Exploring Technology Media Design Writing Code Writing Music

AMIT S. MANGAT

WEB DEVELOPER/CREATIVE DESIGNER

EDUCATION

[International Academy of Design & Technology]

02/2011 - 03/2012

[Learned basic computer skills, hardware and software.] [4.0 GPA – Placed on President's List]

[Indiana University Purdue University Indianapolis]

07/2011 - 06/2012

[Beginner SQL, & HTML/CSS, advanced computing techniques] [3.5GPA – Placed on Dean's List]

[Eleven Fifty Academy]

02/2020 -08/2020]

[Advanced JavaScript, React & Node.js, HTML/CSS, advanced skills working with version control such as Git and deployments with Firebase & Heroku. Advanced experience working with node, building full stack Postgres-Express-React-Node web apps.]

WORK EXPERIENCE

[Best Buy] – [Computer Sales]

06/2016 - 12/2018

[Earned top gun, being the highest sales associate within the district. Provided support and solutions about electronics to everyday personal and professional consumers. Consistent with the completion of target goals assigned daily and monthly.]

[Premium Retail - Oculus] – [Facebook Brand Ambassador]

06/2018 - 02/2020

[Team lead for my territory to build the displays for the Oculus Quest] [Being a brand Ambassador for Facebook, I provided updates and troubleshooting of their devices located in retail stores. As well as promoting their devices, being a face of the company.

[Eleven Fifty Academy] – [JavaScript Web Dev. Learning Assistant] 08/2020 – 02/2021

[Excelling at my role as a learning assistant. Providing students with the understandings of modern-day web development. Providing help through debugging, answering questions, providing resources, guidance towards their success within each cohort.]

CURRENT

[Eleven Fifty Academy] – [JavaScript Web Dev. Instructor Trainee] 02/2021 – Current

[Following a Senior Dev mentor. Taking part in leading lessons, that are provided to the students. Along with adding content to the base curriculum.]

